# Kevin Gerstner



☑ sirkevinicus@gmail.com

github.com/SirKevinicus

314-614-2301

## **Work Experience**

#### **Graphic Design Intern @ ArchCity Defenders**

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019 \\ SAINT LOUIS, MO

- » Made digital art recreation of clients using Photoshop for print and web marketing
- » Created social media graphics, one of which got over 300 shares on Facebook
- » Researched social justice issues and communicated key issues to the affected communities

#### Research Assistant @ University of Tulsa

OCT 2018 - APR 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Researched, co-authored and published a paper with Prof. Sandeep Kuttal entitled: "Remote Pair-Programming in Online CS Education: Investigating through a Gender Lens", which was presented in the 2019 VL/HCC (Visual Languages & Human Centric Computing) conference.

## Game Navigator & Server @ Shuffles Board Game Café SEP 2018 - JAN 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Taught parties of people how to play board games, as well as taking orders and delivering food. In my spare time, I read rule books to learn new games.

## **Projects**

#### **Portfolio Website**

Web Developer \\ 2021 \\ www.kevingerstner.com

- » Designed and coded a portfolio website using HTML, CSS/SASS, Bootstrap 5, and JS
- » Used Netlify to host and Namecheap for domain
- » Worked with web-friendly standards like Responsive Design, WEBM/P files, and Lighthouse

#### **Tomb of Khaibit**

#### Environment Designer & Tools Programmer \\ 2021

- » Created a Unity editor tool called Texo that can make procedurally generated dungeons
- » Made pixel art for the tomb environment using Aseprite

#### Song Pong

#### Feature Developer & Artist \\ 2020

- » Made a rhythm game inspired by the 80s and Pong in three months with the Unity engine
- » Coded features like spawning notes along to the beat and a song editor
- » Created art assets in Illustrator and Blender

#### **Knock-Out! Global Smackdown Board Game**

Board Game Designer & Artist \\ 2018

- » Created over 150 unique card artworks, box art, and graphics for marketing
- » Created a Wordpress website
- » Launched a Kickstarter campaign

## **Summary**

Passionate, well-rounded developer and designer with experience creating C# games in Unity and websites with HTML, SASS, and JS. Will graduate in 2021 with BS Computer Science / Art & Math Minor. Excellent at working with a team to implement ideas to create a finished product. Picks up new skills quickly.

### **Skills**

#### **Programming**

C# · Java · C++ · HTML · CSS/SASS · jQuery · JavaScript

#### **Tools & Platforms**

Unity • Visual Studio • GitHub • ClickUp • Eclipse • Netlify • Word-Press • itch.io

#### Design

Photoshop • Illustrator • InDesign • Figma • Aseprite

## **Education**

## The University of Tulsa 2017 - 2021 \\ TULSA, OK

B.S. in Computer Science and B.S. in Computer Simulation and Gaming with Math and Art minors

## **Certifications**

Unity Certified Associate Game Developer

### Interests

Board Games, Overwatch, Art, Animated movies, Horror Games, Music, Coffee